Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 3 Months

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Afreen Astara (1) Featured

Senior Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Engineering, DevOps, Production Support, Project Management, Mulesoft, Talend, Web Technologies, SQL Server, Unix Scripting, Dynatrace, Jenkins, IIS, Websphere, Weblogic



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer

Current Company: United Health Group

Current Location: Delhi

Pref. Location: Chandigarh, Delhi / NCR, Jaipur

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Mule Esb, Devops, Websphere, WAS Administration, IIS Server, Windows Server, Unix, Shell Scripting, SQL

Server, Jenkins, Dynatrace, Talend, Kanban, Microsoft Azure, Powershell, Rabbitmq, kafka, kubernetes, Docker

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

B.E. (Electronics and Communication) professional with an experience of about 7.3 years in the area of Production/ Application Support, DevOps.

Proficient in Mulesoft, Talend, Jboss, Websphere Application Server, IIS, Weblogic, Apache Tomcat, Microsoft SharePoint 2010 Foundation, , Oracle(SQL) ,MSSQL Server, UNIX, Windows Server, CA Service Desk Manager Tool ,other CA ITSM tools like CA ITCM, CA Introscope, , Tivoli Workload Scheduler (TWS), Connect Direct, Jenkins, Unix shell scripting, XL-release, XLdeploy, Dynatrace, Rabbit Mq, Kafka, Azure, K

Adroit in understanding the applications and providing effective resolution to customer queries related to production support and improving relationships with the customer by anticipating customer future requirements, thereby ensuring a positive customer experience.

Excellent communication & inter-personal skills with abilities in resolving production issues(server and code issues)

Work Experience

United Health Group as Senior Software Engineer Feb 2018 to Till Date

Working as a DevOps professional supporting Production Technical as well as functional issues. Involved in code fix, daily handling of issues, certificate renewal, infrastructure upgrade activities.

Amdocs India Pvt. Ltd. as Technology Integration Engineer - Middleware May 2015 to Feb 2018

Altisource Business Solutions Pvt. Ltd. as Junior Software Engineer Apr 2013 to May 2015

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2012

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Microsoft SharePoint 2010 Foundation			
Toad,Putty, SQL Server Management Studio			
Windows Xp, Windows Server 2003			
Windows Server 2008,UNIX			
SQL			
Shell Script			
MS Excel, MS PowerPoint			
MS FrontPage			
Windows Xp, Windows Server 2003			
MS Access, MS Project			
WebSphere			
WebLogic			
JBoss			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Assamese				

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization